



# ALEJANDRO MARTÍN

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR

- alehamartinva@gmail.com
- +34 671 213 938
- https://alehaaaa.github.io/
- Barcelona. Spain

#### PROFILE

I am a 3D Character Animator with vision and passion. Experienced in production environments, receiving instructions from the Animation Director and Supervisor and collaborating with other Animators and the Rigging team. I am excited to contribute to the industry to warm everyone's heart.

#### EDUCATION

#### EXPERIENCE

### MASTER IN 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION

ECIB | 2021 - 2022

Lip-sync · Advanced Acting

#### **DEGREE IN ANIMATION**

ECIB | 2019 - 2021

2D · StopMotion · 3D

#### ACTING INTRODUCTION EÒLIA THEATER SCHOOL 2021 - 2022

Learnt to embrace a character

## 3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR FOR SHORT FILM BY VÍCTOR MARÍN ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | OCT 2022 - SEP 2023

Project currently in production, working side by side with the Director and Animation Supervisor, bringing ideas to the table.

- Animated and developed character traits, maintaining personalities throughout the story, with the tight guidance of the Supervisor.
- Recorded multiple references, based on the time frame and dialogs.
- Worked on a pose Library whilst animating to test the characters.
- Implemented a production pipeline to organize shots and files, created a variety of tools to streamline the animation process.
- Keeping deliveries according to the established production timeline, always open-minded to changes.

#### SKILLS

M AUTODESK MAYA

**BLENDER** 

A ADOBE SUITE

PYTHON

English (C1, Advanced)
Spanish (Native)
Catalan (Native)

### 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION TEACHER ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | 2023

Taught the animation principles as well as an introduction to 3D animation to first year animation students.

- Accomplished the established academic objectives.
- Dynamized the classroom and assisted them to obtain good looking results in their final projects.